question_data = [
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Gadgets",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Computers",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The Windows 7 operating system has six main editions.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;PAYDAY: The Heist&quot; is a sequel to the board game &quot;Payday&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]